<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Services on Home</title><link>http://growinggreentrees.net/services/</link><description>Recent content in Services on Home</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 13:15:48 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://growinggreentrees.net/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Planting</title><link>http://growinggreentrees.net/services/planting/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2020 10:02:40 -0500</pubDate><guid>http://growinggreentrees.net/services/planting/</guid><description>Our plantings are done by the book. The holes are dug by hand. These new trees look healthier than ever. We have a high success rate and watering and amendment regimen that works!</description></item><item><title>Trimming</title><link>http://growinggreentrees.net/services/trimming/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2020 10:02:50 -0500</pubDate><guid>http://growinggreentrees.net/services/trimming/</guid><description>Most trees have a healthy crown ratio of around 50%. This means that the canopy should start halfway up the tree. No more than 25% of the trees live growth should be trimmed if you want healthy results. We take pride in proper pruning techniques, both aesthetics and health are considered.</description></item><item><title>Removal</title><link>http://growinggreentrees.net/services/removal/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2020 10:02:54 -0500</pubDate><guid>http://growinggreentrees.net/services/removal/</guid><description>Although our business is tailored around long term care for trees and plants, sometimes they just have to come down. A dead tree can become a hazard very quickly. A living tree can pose the same problem. Let us help you decide if removing a tree is a good option for your property.</description></item><item><title>Injection</title><link>http://growinggreentrees.net/services/injection/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2020 10:03:01 -0500</pubDate><guid>http://growinggreentrees.net/services/injection/</guid><description>Our Plant Health Care department is diagnosing and treating trees for a variety of different pests, diseases, and deficiencies. Shown is an injection of an ash tree to prevent and eliminate the invasive emerald ash borer insect.</description></item><item><title>Other</title><link>http://growinggreentrees.net/services/other/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 13:36:16 -0500</pubDate><guid>http://growinggreentrees.net/services/other/</guid><description> Cabling / Bracing Tree support systems Winter protection Mulching Landscape design and installation General landscape maintenance Paver repair Fall / Spring cleanup Storm damage and emergency work Invasive species / Pest ID and abatement Consulting</description></item></channel></rss>